Guide to the United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VII. Office of the Historian
  - Subseries VII.3: Executive Office. Monographs
    - 3a. UNRRA Observers Mission to Korea Report June 14 - Aug.2, Vol. II (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Middle East (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 1. Camps (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 2. Office History (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Netherlands (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 1. UNRRA Mission (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Philippines (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 1. Philippine Mission (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Poland (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 1. Background and Negotiation of the UNRRA-Polish Agreement (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - la. Early History (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 2. Office of Chief (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 3. History of Finance & Administration Department (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 4. Division of Organization & Management (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 5. Administrative Services (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 6. Accounts Division (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 7. Mission Transport Branch (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 8. Communications Division (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 9. Registration, Training and Placing the Disabled (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 10. Welfare Supplies (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 11. Child Care (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 12. Operational Analysis (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 13. Public Information (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 14. Supply Department (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 15. Textiles & Clothing (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 16. Food & Agriculture (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 16a. Food (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 17. Distribution Division (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 17a. Distribution Division Material (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 18. Supply Accounting & Statistical Division (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 19. Historical Report on Industrial Rehabilitation Division (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 20. INter-Mission Training (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 21. Medical Mission (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 22. Regional Office (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 23. Port office, Dnydia-Gdansh (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 24. Voluntary Societies in Poland (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 25. Social Services in Poland (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 26. Quaker Relief and Unitarian Service Committee (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - SWPA (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 1. Forward (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 2. Preface (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 3. Early Commitments (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 4. SWPA Offoce (1) (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 5. SWPA Office (2) (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 6. Lapstone Conference (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 7. Relations with the Australian Government (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 8. Relations with the Australian Government, 1946-7 (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 9. Relations with New Zealand Government (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 10. Finance 1945 (Box H/15, Folder Side 2)
    - 11. Finance 1946 (Box H/16, Folder Side 1)
    - 12. Finance 1947 (Box H/16, Folder Side 1)
    - 13. Accounts (Box H/16, Folder Side 1)
    - 14. Establishment a-1 Organization of the: Supply Division (Box H/16, Folder Side 1)
    - 15. Procurement in Australia 1945 (Box H/16, Folder Side 1)
    - 16. The Reorganization of the Supply Division (Box H/16, Folder Side 1)
    - 17. Procurement in New Zealand 1945-6 (Box H/16, Folder Side 1)
    - 18. Procurement in Australia 1946-7 (Box H/16, Folder Side 1)
    - 19. Procurement in New Zealand 1946-7 (Box H/16, Folder Side 1)
    - 20. Recruitment for Europe 1945 (Box H/16, Folder Side 1)
    - 21. Appendices (Box H/16, Folder Side 1)
    - 22. Activities of the Health Division in SWPA (Box H/16, Folder Side 1)
    - Switzerland (Box H/16, Folder Side 1)
    - 1. Historical Report (Box H/16, Folder Side 1)
    - Ukraine (Box H/16, Folder Side 1)
    - 1. Historical Report (Box H/16, Folder Side 1)
    - Yugoslavia (Box H/16, Folder Side 1)
    - 1. Volume I (Box H/16, Folder Side 1)
    - 2. Vol. II (Box H/16, Folder Side 1)
    - 3. Vol. III (Box H/16, Folder Side 1)
    - 4. Vol. IV (Box H/16, Folder Side 1)
    - 4a. Vol. IVa (Box H/16, Folder Side 1)
    - 5. Vol. V (Box H/16, Folder Side 1)
    - 6. Vol. VI (Box H/16, Folder Side 1)
    - 6a. Vol. VIa (Box H/16, Folder Side 1)
    - 6b. Vol. VIb (Box H/16, Folder Side 1)
    - 6b. Vol. VIb (Box H/16, Folder Side 2)
    - 6c. Vol. VIc (Box H/16, Folder Side 2)
    - 6d. Vol. VId (Box H/16, Folder Side 2)
    - 6e. Vol. VIe (Box H/16, Folder Side 2)
    - 6f. Vol. VIf (Box H/16, Folder Side 2)
    - 7. Vol. VII (Box H/16, Folder Side 2)
- Series VIII. Office of Public Information
  - Subseries VIII.1: Executive Office. Press Releases
    - Press Release (Box PI/1, Folder Side 1)
    - 1st Council Session (Box PI/1, Folder Side 1)
    - 2nd Council Session (Box PI/1, Folder Side 1)
    - 4th Council Session (Box PI/1, Folder Side 1)
    - 5th Council Session (Box PI/1, Folder Side 1)
    - 6th Council Session (Box PI/1, Folder Side 1)
    - 1944 (Box PI/1, Folder Side 1)
    - 1945, #1-99 (Box PI/1, Folder Side 1)
    - 1945, #100-199 1945, #200-299 1945, #300-399 (Box PI/1, Folder Side 1)
    - 1945. #400-478 (Box PI/1, Folder Side 1)
    - 1946. #1-99 (Box PI/1, Folder Side 1)
    - 1946, #100-199 (Box PI/1, Folder Side 1)
    - 1946, #200-299 (Box PI/1, Folder Side 1)
    - 1946, #300-399 (Box PI/1, Folder Side 1)
    - 1946, #400-499 (Box PI/1, Folder Side 1)
    - 1946, #500-558 (Box PI/1, Folder Side 1)
    - 553.2 1947-50 (Box PI/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Community Canning Program for War Relief (Box PI/1, Folder Side 1)
    - United National Clothing Collection (Box PI/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Victory Clothing Collection (Box PI/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Victory Collection of Canned Food (Box PI/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Special Release for Radio Farm Directors No. 1-15, 1 Nov. 1945- 8 Aug. 1946 (Box PI/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Special Release to Women's Program Directors 1-30 (Box PI/1, Folder Side 1)
    - ERO Press Conference, July 1944-Jan. 1946 (Box PI/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Numerical Lists, 1944-7 (Box PI/1, Folder Side 1)
- Series IX. Secretariat Executive Office
  - Subseries IX.1: Subject File
    - Administrative Order Work Sheets (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Administrative Services (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement, Multi-lateral Draft (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement, Mimeo Agreements, Correspondence, etc. (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - American Jewish Committee (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - American Red Cross (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - American Relief Administration (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Announcements of Appointments of Administrative and Secretariat Personnel (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Area Program Material (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Bases of Requirements (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Budget & Accounting Procedures (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Bulletin Notes (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Bureau of Finance & Administration (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Bureau of Services (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Bureau of Supply (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Cablegram Procedures (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Clothing (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Combined Boards (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Committee, Abolition of (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Committee (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Standing Technical Committee Members (Gov't Letters) Relationship between Technical Committee and Subcommittee (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Rules of Procedure for Committee (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Rules of Procedure for the Council & Observers (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Secretaries, Appointment of (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Correspondence on Ability to Pay (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Subcommittee (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - on Ability to Pay (General) (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - on Ability to Pay (General Correspondence and Information) (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Staley, Ability to Pay (Miller Memo) (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Subcommittee on Determination of Ability to Pay (Organization of) (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Ability to Pay for R.R. Foreign Exchange (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Ability to Pay (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - China (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Czechoslovakia (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Ethiopia (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Greece (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Philippines (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - USSR (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Committee on Agriculture (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Standing Technical Committee on Agricultural Correspondence (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Standing Technical Committee on Agricultural Correspondence (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Audit Subcommittee Originals '47 (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Central Committee Document, Originals (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - China Program Committee (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Standing Technical Committee, Displaced Persons (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Committee on the Council of Europe (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Technical Subcommittee for Europe (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Committee for Far East, Meetings, Designations, etc. (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Committee on Financial Control, General Correspondence and Information (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Ad Hoc Subcommittee on Food (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Standing Technical Committee on Health of the Council (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Standing Technical Subcommittee on the International Children's Fund (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - 1st Meeting (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Technical Regional Subcommittees (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Committee on Supplies Committee on Supplies, General Correspondence, Policy, Functions (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Members, etc. (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Committee on Training for China (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Standing Technical Subcommittee on Welfare for Europe (Box SE/1, Folder Side 1)
    - Standing Technical Subcommittee on Welfare for Europe (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Ad Hoc Subcommittee on Welfare for the Far East (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Conferences (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Congress, Relations with (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Contributions from Member Gov'ts (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Cooperatives (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - 1st Council Session (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - 2nd Council Session (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - 5th Council Session (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Council VI Reports of Work (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - 7th Council Session, Materials on (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Country Program (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Credentials of Member Gov'ts Representatives to the first Session of the Council of UNRRA: Credentials (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Observers (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Belgium (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Bolivia (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Byelorussia S.S.R. (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Chile (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Colombia (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Costa Rica (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Cuba (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Czechoslovakia (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Denmark (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Dominican Republic (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Ecuador (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Egypt (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - El Salvador (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Ethiopia (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Greece (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Guatemala (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Haiti (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Honduras (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Iceland (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - India (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Iran (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Iraq (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Liberia (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Luxembourg (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Mexico (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Netherlands (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - New Zealand (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Nicaragua (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Norway (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Panama (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Paraguay (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Peru (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Philippines Commonwealth (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Poland (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Ukrainian S.S.R. (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Union of South Africa (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Uruguay (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Venezuela (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Dr. Dai's Correspondence (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Data for Director General's Quarterly Report (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - D.G. Report to Clearance Correspondence (C.C.) Jan-Dec. 1945 (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - D.G. Report to C.C. Jan-Dec 1946 (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - D.G. Report to C.C. Jan-Oct 1947 (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - D.G. Report - Clearance Correspondence (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Displaced Persons (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Displaced Populations (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Distribution (UNRRA Supplies) (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Bistibution Office (Documents) (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Division of Reports (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Docket Book - Cables (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Docket Book - Correspondence up to Sept. 1, 1944 (Box SE/1, Folder Side 2)
    - Docket Book (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Correspondence Sept, 1-Dec. 1944 (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - UNRRA Correspondence Jan.1-Junel, 1945 (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Distribution of Documents (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Personnel, Reports and Divisional Reports (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Far Eastern Region (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Far Eastern Staff Meetings (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Fellowships (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Field Missions (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Field Reporting (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Food (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Foreign Economic Administration (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Foreign Mission 3rd Person Notes (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - General Council Memoranda (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Glossary of Terms (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Governments, Relations with (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Dr. Gullick (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Letters December-January (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Letters February-November (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Memorandums (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Health Division Misc. (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Health and Medical (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Health Program (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Historians, Appointment of (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Historians, Preservation of Records (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Historians' Office (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Industrial Rehabilitation (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Institute of International Service (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Institute of Pacific Relations (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Institute of Pacific Relations (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Intellectual Cooperation, Committee on (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Intelligence Liaison Service (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Intergovernmental Committee on Refugees (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - Internal Advisory Committee (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - International Administration International Conferences (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - International Administration Training Programs (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - International Children's Emergency Fund (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - International Document Service (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - International Labor Office (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - International Labor Office (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - ILO Conference (Box SE/2, Folder Side 1)
    - International Monetary Conference (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - International Monetary Fund (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - International Refugees Organization (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - International Sanitary Conventions (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Journals (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - League of Nations (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Legal Opinions (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Leith Ross, Report to Allied Gov'ts. (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Library (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Library Advisory Committee (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Library, L. Wilmerding, Jr. Report (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Library, Transfer of UNRRA Library to UN (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Logistics of European Relief (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Mail and Records Procedures (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Manual for Committees Secretaries - Worksheets (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Measures (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Members of the Council 1944-6 (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Merra (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Military, Relations with (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Miscelleneous (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Miscelleneous Correspondence (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Misc. Memeo July 1947 (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Mission to the American Republics - Santos Mission (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Near East Foundation Notes on Interviews (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Observers (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Organizational UNRRA (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Charts (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Organizations and Functions (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel Division (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Personnel Management Manual (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Press Conferences (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Private Organizations, Relations with (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Privileges and Immunities (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Czechoslovakia (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - India (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Misc. (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Palestine (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - South Africa (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - U.K. and Canada (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - USA (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - UNRRA Policy on (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Procedure Control (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Procedural Secretariat (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Program Material (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Progress Report, Secretariat (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Jan.-July 1944 (inclusive), Aug-Dec 1944 (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Vol. I, 1-12 (#10 never issued) 1945 (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Vol. II, 1-9 1946 (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Public Information Office (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Publications of UNRRA (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Refugee Camps (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Relief Requirements, European Area (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Secretariat (Monograph Staff Meetings) (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Selected Documents 124.1 (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Senior Deputy D.G. Office (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Speeches or Articles, Correspondence (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Steere, Lloyd, Material (Box SE/2, Folder Side 2)
    - Subjects and Reports outside (Box SE/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Symbol System (Box SE/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Training Branch (Box SE/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Transportation Problems and Policy in Relation to Relief & Rehabilitation (Box SE/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Travel Procedures (Box SE/3, Folder Side 1)
    - United Nations (Box SE/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Conference on Peace and Security at San Francisco (Box SE/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Economic and Social Council (Box SE/3, Folder Side 1)
    - UNESCO (Box SE/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Food & Agricultural Organization (Box SE/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Liaison Committee on Int'l Education (Box SE/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Relations with US Government Agencies (Box SE/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Resolution #88 (Box SE/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Working Group for Asia & Far East of Temporary Subcommission on Economic Reconciliation of Devastated Areas (Box SE/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Unnumbered Document 1944 (Box SE/3, Folder Side 1)
    - 1945 (Box SE/3, Folder Side 1)
    - 1946 (Box SE/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Voluntary Agencies (Box SE/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Welfare, Division of (Box SE/3, Folder Side 1)
    - Wheat Import Requirements (Box SE/3, Folder Side 1)
    - World Health Organization (Box SE/3, Folder Side 1)
    - World Jewish Congress (Box SE/3, Folder Side 1)